{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822231051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822231051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822231290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822231289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822231745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822231744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822232193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822232192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822232506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822232506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822233300","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822233300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822233893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822233893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822234136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822234136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822234939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822234939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822237184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822237184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822237293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822237293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" d2619eec-9828-4a76-83da-b7d99523cc40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822243222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822243222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" 16a9a05a-3617-4850-a53e-d265fc61f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822258744","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822258743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" 16a9a05a-3617-4850-a53e-d265fc61f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822261294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822261294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" 16a9a05a-3617-4850-a53e-d265fc61f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822261407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822261406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211013"," gameId":" 16a9a05a-3617-4850-a53e-d265fc61f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"end":"end"}]}